I've got a bit of a confession to make,
and you would not expect this to come out
of my mouth. There used to be a time
that I was too proud to steal,
and I thought
stealing ideas was bad. And there
was even a person called Adam Sullivan,
who is an
Australian personal trainer entrepreneur,
and he was stealing from me.
My ideas, my videos. I
was getting sent them,
and my way of coping with that was to
block him. And at the time,
I thought it was because I
was trying to protect my
ideas, but actually now,
being a bit more mature and older,
I look back, I was
jealous of him because he had taken my
ideas and done better with
them than I could ever have imagined.
He would've had some months where he
was making more money in a four-week
period
than I was making in a year,
and I didn't like that,
so I decided to block him.
Then a few years later,
we're speaking at the same event.
The guy running the event says, "Oi,
he's actually a good dude." Let me show
you
Adam quickly.
Adam grew up in a part of Sydney with not
a lot of money, and he's a
self-made multimillionaire.
He's actually now one of my very good
friends.
Two things I've learned from Adam.
One,
he helped me be okay with buying nice
things and publicly showing
it off because I think I went through a
period of my life, because I'm British,
where I didn't want to have nice things
because I thought people might hate me for
it.
And then only seeing Adam with his nice
things, I actually realized the people
that are your true OGs
that want to see you do well,
they want to see you do well.
And now I look at Adam
and all the things
that he stole from me idea-wise, I'm
happy for him and I'm proud of him in some
sense because this is how things
work. Quite literally, nothing
is original.
If you're not looking
and monitoring as to what is doing well,
thinking of
doing it yourself,
you're not going to survive. Yesterday,
I put out a reel.
It's about Ronda Patrick being a fucking
idiot about the smoothie and banana
incident. Want to know how that happened?
Saw the reel.
Thought, "Oh,
that's stupid." Saw a reaction to it.
Thought, "Oh yeah,
that's stupid." Saw another reaction to
it, and I was like,
"Hold on, there's a pattern emerging.
It's time for me to jump on this trend."
What did I do?
I went and I looked at some of the
best-performing reels, created my own,
boom, put
it out. I thieved what
was already working.